# **Igor Franciuc, Frontend Developer**

E-mail: <a href="mailto:igor.franciuc@gmail.com">igor.franciuc@gmail.com</a>
Phone: +373 69 054 697
Telegram: <a href="mailto:https://t.me/lfeerus">https://t.me/lfeerus</a>

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/igor-franchiuc-890308242

Website: <a href="https://igor-franchiuc.netlify.app/">https://igor-franchiuc.netlify.app/</a>

Chisinau (Moldova).



### About me

I have experience in creating website layouts, where I honed my HTML, CSS and JavaScript skills. However, I want to grow and I think it would be more effective for me to become a member of a friendly team as a Frontend Developer.

I have studied React, Javascript, HTML, CSS and am currently mastering TypeScript. In my free time I love to learn new technologies, create pet projects, play the guitar and go to the gym.

I'm ready to work, learn, get better and grow every day with great people.

## **Skills**

### **Technical Skills**

React, JavaScript, TypeScript, Redux, Next.js, HTML, CSS/SCSS, JQuery, Webpack, MySql, PHP, Git, Figma, Photoshop.

## Language Skills

Russian (mother tongue), English (B2), Romanian (B2)

#### **Soft Skills**

Open to communication, a team player, receptive to learning, reserved, reasonable.

## **Work Experience**

# **SANtech (Frontend Developer - internship)**

May, 2022 — July, 2022

Learning the basics of web development. Stack: HTML, CSS/SCSS, JavaScript

# Studio Webmaster (Web Developer)

August, 2022 — November, 2022

Experience in rebuilding websites and developing online stores.

Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

#### Web Developer (VVT Group Inc.)

May, 2023 — April, 2024

Website development for US clients. Creating lendings, multi-page websites, working with hosting and mail. Stack: HTML, CSS/SCSS, JavaScript, React.js, Next.js, Redux

# **Education**

## **Higher education**

September, 2021 — Current

Applied Informatics, Technical University of Moldova (https://utm.md/), Chisinau (Moldova)

# Courses

September, 2022 — February, 2023

"A complete course in JavaScript + React - from scratch to results" by Ivan Petrichenko (<a href="https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-1dc80c7e-c9eb-4bc5-bbfe-65b8f064eb70/">https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-1dc80c7e-c9eb-4bc5-bbfe-65b8f064eb70/</a>), Chisinau (Moldova) September, 2017 — May, 2020

English courses: "Basic English", Chisinau (Moldova)